Guide to the Hasia Diner Papers, 1970-2012 MC.153
New York University Archives
- Series I: Research Notes
  - Subseries F: Lower East Side Memories
    - The Jazz Singer- notes and copies, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Permission for Photos, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Hester Street Film, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Images for LES, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - FOX permission for Simpsons, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - UAHC Notes, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Information on Maude Weisser's Minatures, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Maude Weisser's Minature's- color photos, undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Maude Weisser's Minatures- black and white photos, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Maude Weisser's Minatures- negatives, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Leo's Delancey Street Deli Photos, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Floppy Disks, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Subseries G: We Remember with Reverance and Love
    - Hebrew Publishing, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - The New York Review, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - New Directions in Jewish Theology in America booklet, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - The Americanization of the Holocaust booklet, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Materials from YIVO, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Art Resource Information, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Permissions for Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Yeshiva Flatbush Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Newberry Library Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - SAJ Permissions, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - American Jewish Historical Society Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Shengold Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Archives Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Book Annual, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - American Jewish Historical Society SCA, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - List of Sources, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Meyer Barkai Permissions, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - URJ Press Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - United Synagogue Commission Permission, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Bloch Publishing Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Temple University Archives Photocopies, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Spertus Permissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - YIVO User Agreements, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Newspaper Clipping, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Yeshiva University Archive Material, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Renee and Chaim Gross Foundation, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Tamiment Archives Premissions, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Carnegie Mellon Libraries, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Cover of the Book, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - NYU Press Copy Edit Info, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Sentinel photocopies, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Images for Book, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Beth Halpen's Master Thesis, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Mia Sara Bruch's Presentation on American Jews, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Naomi Sage Paper, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Kenneth Waltzer Paper, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Laura Jockusch Dissertation Proposal, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Dana Herman Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Carpenter Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Gershon Greenberg Paper, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Natalia Aleksium Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - David Biale Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Holocaust Education Week in Toronto Essay, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - David Weinstein Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Michael Marrus Paper, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Yigal Sklarin Paper, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Purple Notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Red Notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Bobcat Records, undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - The 2001 SWIG Lecture Pamphlet (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Center for Jewish History Photocopy Request, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Tamiment Library Photocopy Requests, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - The Chronicle Review, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Center for Jewish History Request Forms, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Sources used, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - NYPL Records, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Book Reviews, undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Sources that were too early or too late, undated (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - "Junk", undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Israel Goldberg, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fanny Goldstein Papers (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Fanny Goldstein Papers (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Eliezer Greenberg, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Meyer Greenberg Papers, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Halevy Choral Society, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Book Annual (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Book Annual (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Community Council Greater Washington, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Education Magazine (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Education Magazine (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Family and Children Services, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hebrew Union College Annual, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Intercollegiate Zionist and Federation of America, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Louis Harap Material, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Camp Hemshekh, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Rhea Hirsch, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Holocaust Relates Articles in Yiddish Journals, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Jewish Forum Material, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Frontier notes and copies, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Frontier (Original copy), 1958 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Labor Committee (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Jewish Labor Committee (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Jewish Museum- notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Jewish Reconstruction Foundation Papers, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Social Studies Quarterly (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Social Studies Quarterly (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Jewish Spectator (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Jewish Spectator (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Jewish Student Organizations Collection, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency News, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary Misc., undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Jewish War Veterans, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - American Joint Distribution Committee, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Judaism (Quarterly), undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Label Katz Papers (1of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Label Katz Papers (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Labor Zionist Organization of American (Chicago) (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Labor Zionist Organization of America (Chicago) (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Louis Lamed Papers, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Kolbuszowa Relief Association, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Lema'an Hayeled, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Raphael Lempkin papers, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Leo Baeck Institute, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Menorah Journal Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Midstream Magazine (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Midstream Magazine (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Midwest Jewish Council, undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Joseph Baron Papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Salo Baron Papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein (1 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bernstein (2 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bernstein (3 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bernstein (4 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - American Memorial to the 6 million, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Organization League, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Artists, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1954-1967) (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1954-1967) (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - American Jewish Historical Society, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1945-1953) (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1945-1953) (2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - American Jewish Congress (1 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - American Jewish Congress (2 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - American Jewish Congress (3 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - American Jewish Congress (4 of 4), undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Paul Abelson Papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Academy Memoirs, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Bessie Adel Papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - American Federation for Polish Jews, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - American Jewish Committees, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - American Jewish Archives, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - World Over Magazine, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Yiddish Journal, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Studies in Contemporary Jewry, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Songbook of the Cejwin Camps, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Songbook of the Cejwin Camps, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Yiddish Journal, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - P'tsah B'Zemer Songbook, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Journal of Modern Jewish Studies, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - "Polish Historiography of the Holocaust" article, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Seder Service Booklet, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - East European Jewish Affairs Journal, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - AJHS Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Holocaust Commemoration in Vancouver, BC, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - "In the Bond of Life Article', undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Seder Ritual Committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Shalom Aleichem Folk Foundation, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Leo Schwartz Papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Slomowitz papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Synagogue Council of America (1 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Synagogue Council of America (2 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Synagogue Council of America (3 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Synagogue Council of America (4 of 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sophie Tucker Papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Union Institute, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Vaad Hatzalah, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - The Week in Religion, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Women of Reform Judaism Papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Howard Weinshell Papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin Society for Jewish Learning, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Yad Vashem (1 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Yad Vashem (2 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Yad Vashem (3 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Yad Vashem (4 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Yad Vashem (5 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Yad Vashem (6 of 6), undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (1 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (2 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (3 of 3), undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Young Judea (The Senior) (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Young Judea (The Senior) (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Young Israel, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Maurice Zigmond, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Youth and Nation, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Zionist Organization of America pamphlets, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - A 1945-1962 Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - B, C 1945-1962 Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - D, E, F, G 1945-1962 Books (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - D, E, F, G 1945-1962 Books (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - H, I, J 1945-1962 Books (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - H, I, J 1945-1962 Books (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - N, O, P 1945-1962 Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - T, U, V 1945-1962 Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - W, X, Y, Z 1945-1962 Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - G-M Post 1962 Books (1 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - G-M Post 1962 Books (2 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - N-S Post 1962 Books (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - N-S Post 1962 Bokos (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - N-S Post 1962 (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - T-Z Post 1962, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Minkoff (1 of 3), undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Minkoff (2 of 3), undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Minkoff (3 of3), undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Misc. for Ch. 3, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Magazine (1 of 3), undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Magazines (2 of 3), undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Magazines (3 of3), undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Music, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Paul Moni, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Federation of Temple Sisterhoods (1 of2), undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - National Federation of Temple Sisterhoods (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - National Federation of Temple Youth, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - National Jewish Music Council, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Paul O'Dwyer, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Olin Sang Ruby, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - ORT, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Jacob Pat, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - The Pedagogic Reporter, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Josh Perelman, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Koppel Pinson Papers, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Molly Picon, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Plays, Pageant, Cantata, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Joachim Prinz (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Joachim Prinz (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Rabbinical Council of America (Holiday Sermons), undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Ramah, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Cecilia Razovsky, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Religious Zionists of America, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Rescue Children, INC, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Bernard Richards, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Robison Family Papers, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Rode F. Shalom, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - William F. Rosenblum, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Isaac Rosenfeld, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Herman Rubenovitz, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Society for the Advancement of Judaism, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Boris Molar (Between You and Me) (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Boris Molar (Between You and Me) (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Schallek News, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Schappes (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Schappes (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Dore Scharry, undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Hyman Schulson, undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Shalom Secunda, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - NYPL Receipts, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Archives Publication Form, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Jewish Newspaper Project, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Articles A-B, unknown (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Copies of Articles C-D, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Copies of Articles E-F, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Copies of Articles G, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Copies of Articles H-K, unknown (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Copies of Articles L-M, unknown (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Copies of Articles N-P, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Copies of Articles R, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Copies of Articles S, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Copies of Articles T-Y, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Articles 1945-1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Articles Post 1962 (1of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Articles Post 1962 (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Book Reviews (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Thesis Approval Sheet: Carl Samuel Choper, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Chapter 5 of Diane Leon-Ferdico's Thesis, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Picking up the Pieces Thesis, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Select Pages from Laura Jackson's Thesis, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Jason Kalman Thesis Chapter 5, unknown (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Cover page of Cecile Esther Kuznitz's thesis, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Holocaust Art in America Essay, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "Delayed Pilgrims" Roberta Newman thesis (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - 'Delayed Pilgrims" by Roberta Newman thesis (2 of2), undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - American Responses to Holocaust Essay, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - "Defining Lessons" by Rona Sheramy, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Lists of Films, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "Forward", undated (Box 24, File 2)
    - Lillian Friedberg Papers, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Friedman, Philip (1of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Friedman, Philip (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Fardar, S and G, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Furrows (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Furrows (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Commentary Magazine Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Congregation Tifereth Joseph, Anshei Prezemysl (notes), undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Congress for Jewish Culture, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Emails regarding the book, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Conservative Judaism Journal, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Debrest, Harold, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Der Tog, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Eternal Light (1 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Eternal Light (2 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Eternal Light (3 of 3), undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Calemson, Jesse, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cantor's Institute, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Centre de Documentation Juive Contemp. In Paris, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Central Orthodox Committee, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cincinnati JCRC (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cincinnati JCRC (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Claims Conference, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Cogan, Edna, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Jacob, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Bibliographies, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Bletter, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Bloch Publishing, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - B'nai Brith, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - B'hai B'rith Waukesha, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Rabbi Isadore Breslau, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Busker, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Subseries H. Roads Taken
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name A-D, 1986-2012 (Box 25)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name D-H, 1986-2012 (Box 26)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name H-L, 1986-2012 (Box 27)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name L-N, 1986-2012 (Box 28)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name N-R, 1986-2012; cuid19079
      - Paper Materials (Box 29)
      - Papernick, Bernie -- Ontario Jewish Archive, UA_MC_153_ER_1
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name R-Z and Author Not Listed, 1986-2012 (Box 30)
    - Roads Taken Research: No Author Listed, Images, 1986-2012 (Box 31)
    - Roads Taken Research Notes, 1986-2012 (Box 32)
    - Roads Taken Unpublished Draft, 1986-2012 (Box 33)